

Contact Information

+380683985358

mrit.works07@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin</u>

GlitHub

<u>Telegram</u>

Ukraine

Tech Skills

HTML

CSS

SCSS

Git

JavaScript

React

Redux

React-router

Agile

Scrum

Soft Skills

Approachable

Organized

Initiative

Communicative

Energetic

Languages

English Intermediate

Ukrainian Native

Russian Native

Peredrii Yevhenii

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (React)

Hi, my name is Yevhenii, I'm 30 years old,I like to work in a team and learn something new. I completed courses at the Golt school. I have a good understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React have an analytical mindset, quickly memorize new information, and are not afraid of constructive criticism.

Work Experience



Student Goit

September 2021 - May 2022 I'm taking a course at the goit academy, in the directionof JavaScript and React.



Manager

2014-2016

Worked in the BF company, as a Team Leader, there were five people under the leadership

Project experience

M<u>y personal website HTML- CSS</u>

<u>Ice shop</u> <u>SCSS</u>

<u>Cinema library</u> <u>JavaScrip</u>t

<u>Family wallet</u> React JS

Education

Kharkiv Motor Transport

College - Specialist

Mechanic

September 2010 - May 2014